<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; Notebookish</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/uncategorized/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 06:42:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>10 Beautiful Book Blogs to Follow</title>
		<link>/2025/01/19/10-beautiful-book-blogs-to-follow/</link>
					<comments>/2025/01/19/10-beautiful-book-blogs-to-follow/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 06:42:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=314</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There are so many book blogs, all very good. The book blogging world is one of the oldest and bustling,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are so many book blogs, all very good. The book blogging world is one of the oldest and bustling, close-knit communities, way before Bookstagram (Bookish community on Instagram), Book Twitter, Booktube (Bookish community on Youtube) and other social media communities gained prominence. Book blogs are old souls. They save you with short recommendations and long essays, rambling posts and pictures of lovely stacks on the nightstand. In the present times, the walls of book blogging have expanded to accommodate literary travel, literary lifestyle, bookish hygge and cosy reading nights. It is difficult to choose a few blogs for a list because there are so many wonderful ones, and of course many more that I myself visit often. Here are some stylish book blogs that are aesthetically pleasing, have clean and thoughtful designs, and post great content including book recommendations, literary travel and more. Be it honest book talk or drop-dead gorgeous book photography or easy navigation, these definitely spark joy. You will find some of the best book blogs that’ll help you decide whether a new book is for you, blogs that talk about monetizing blogging and those that help you do some arm chair travelling with a book.</p><h2 class="wp-block-heading">Best Book Blogs to Follow</h2><p>Book pictures, essays, book lists—these have got it all.</p><h3 class="wp-block-heading">1.&nbsp;<a href="http://www.whatshotblog.com/">What’s Hot Blog</a></h3><p>Laura is one of my oldest friends on Instagram and I love how wonderfully she juggles her career as a lawyer with travel, café hops and truckloads of books. She is also one of the sweetest and most helpful people out there, always willing to give out advice, help you when you are stuck for inspiration or even to have a quick chat about a book. One of Laura’s best qualities is how she is passionate about the things she believes in and writes comprehensive, in-depth guides to share her knowledge and experience. Her ‘<a href="https://whatshotblog.com/its-time-for-book-bloggers-and-bookstagrammers-to-get-paid/">It is time for bloggers and bookstagrammers to get paid</a>’ was one of the most honest stories on the topic. If you are looking to monetize your blog, start with&nbsp;<a href="https://whatshotblog.com/affiliate-marketing-for-book-bloggers/">The ultimate affiliate marketing guide for book bloggers</a>. If you are trying to get used to working from home, here are Laura’s&nbsp;<a href="https://whatshotblog.com/working-from-home-tips/">practical tips</a>. She also shares amazing brunch locations, beautiful travel plans, TV guides, book lists and lifestyle posts, all with stunning photography on&nbsp;<em>What’s Hot</em>.</p><figure class="wp-block-image" id="attachment_8346"><a href="http://whatshotblog.com/"><img decoding="async" src="https://thebooksatchel.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/whatshotblog.jpg" alt="Best Book Blogs What's hot Blog" class="wp-image-8346"/></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Image by Laura | What’s Hot Blog</figcaption></figure><h3 class="wp-block-heading">2. Juliet’s library</h3><p>I discovered Juliet’s stunning blog recently. I was very much drawn by her beautiful, well styled pictures. If you need a crash course on book photography, spend a few minutes browsing her photos. Minutes will turn into hours, I warn you from experience. Juliet is a part time editor who loves books, and quietness of cities. She enjoys exploring the neighbourhood for good coffeeshops. Her reading lists are great places to find new books—brief and to-the-point, accompanied by her bookish photos. Start with Juliet’s&nbsp;summer reading list&nbsp;or her&nbsp;<a href="https://www.instagram.com/julietslibrary/?hl=en">Instagram guide to New York city</a>.</p><figure class="wp-block-image" id="attachment_8343"><a href="https://pinterest.com/pin/create/bookmarklet/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.thebooksatchel.com%2Fbest-book-blogs-to-follow%2F&amp;media=https%3A%2F%2Fthebooksatchel.com%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2F2020%2F10%2FJuliets-Library.jpg&amp;description=Image%20by%20Juliet%20%7C%20Juliet%E2%80%99s%20Library&amp;is_video=false" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img decoding="async" src="https://thebooksatchel.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/Juliets-Library.jpg" alt="Juliet's Library" class="wp-image-8343"/></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Image by Juliet | Juliet’s Library</figcaption></figure><h3 class="wp-block-heading">3. The Ardent Biblio</h3><p>I first came across&nbsp;<em>The Ardent Biblio</em>&nbsp;when I was featured along with them in Blogosphere-Issue 19. I immediately fell in love with the clean, minimal website and striking, breath taking pictures where the books look so good that you can almost eat them. For example LOOK at this&nbsp;<a href="https://www.theardentbiblio.com/blog/2020/5/15/fall-preview-2020">Fall publishing preview 2020</a>&nbsp;(have you ever seen anything more gorgeous? Good food and shiny, new books?).&nbsp;<em>The Ardent Biblio</em>&nbsp;is run by Rikki and Michaela—you’ll get recommendations from both of them. The website focusses on literary lifestyle where reading is a way of life. So you’ll find book recommendations based on mood—<a href="https://www.theardentbiblio.com/blog/2020/8/19/what-were-reading-this-fall-off-our-shelves-edition">fall reading from the shelves</a>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a href="https://www.theardentbiblio.com/blog/2019/6/11/summer-reading-when-you-crave-that-summertime-sadness">books for summer sadness</a>.</p><figure class="wp-block-image" id="attachment_8344"><a href="https://pinterest.com/pin/create/bookmarklet/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.thebooksatchel.com%2Fbest-book-blogs-to-follow%2F&amp;media=https%3A%2F%2Fthebooksatchel.com%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2F2020%2F10%2Ftheardentbiblio.jpg&amp;description=Image%20by%20The%20Ardent%20Biblio&amp;is_video=false" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img decoding="async" src="https://thebooksatchel.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/theardentbiblio.jpg" alt="Best Book Blogs—The Ardent Biblio" class="wp-image-8344"/></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Image by The Ardent Biblio</figcaption></figure><h3 class="wp-block-heading">4. The Literary Edit</h3><p>Lucy, who runs&nbsp;<em>The Literary Edit</em>, is an old friend. I am amazed how consistently beautiful her posts are. Whether she is talking about books or strolling at the Bondi beach or reading in a bathtub, she manages to capture quiet, serene pictures that really make you want to shut yourself from the world and curl up with a book. She also runs a monthly book club, The Bondi Literary Salon. One of Lucy’s best features is&nbsp;<a href="https://thelitedit.com/category/desert-island-books/">Desert Island books</a>&nbsp;where she asks readers, authors, bloggers about their picks if they are stranded on an island. Or start with&nbsp;<a href="https://thelitedit.com/my-very-favourite-books/">Lucy’s favourite books</a>&nbsp;and indulge in window gazing at the most&nbsp;<a href="https://thelitedit.com/category/beautiful-bookstores/">beautiful bookstores</a>.</p><figure class="wp-block-image" id="attachment_8345"><a href="https://pinterest.com/pin/create/bookmarklet/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.thebooksatchel.com%2Fbest-book-blogs-to-follow%2F&amp;media=https%3A%2F%2Fthebooksatchel.com%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2F2020%2F10%2Fthelitedit.jpg&amp;description=Image%20by%20Lucy%20Pearson%20%7C%20The%20Literary%20Edit&amp;is_video=false" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img decoding="async" src="https://thebooksatchel.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/thelitedit.jpg" alt="The Literary Edit" class="wp-image-8345"/></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Image by Lucy Pearson | The Literary Edit</figcaption></figure><h3 class="wp-block-heading">5. Books and Bao</h3><p>Jessica and Will are digital nomads, and writers. They love love cat-sitting, books, plays and video games (that’s Will). The world is their home, so you’ll always find them tweeting from different cities, urging you to pick up fantastic, underrated translated gems or shining a spotlight on authors and translators (a lovely archive to work your way through). They also note down their recommendations in literary travel guides, which is a treat to read. Want to visit a country?—read these books! Some of my favourites at&nbsp;<em>Books and Bao</em>&nbsp;include&nbsp;<a href="https://booksandbao.com/reading-manga-places-to-start/">Where to start with manga</a>&nbsp;,&nbsp;<a href="https://booksandbao.com/culinary-guide-to-south-korea/">a culinary guide to South Korea</a>&nbsp;(if I can’t fulfill my dream of a South Korean food crawl inspired by the K-dramas that consume me, I’ll enjoy it vicariously through Will and Jess), and&nbsp;<a href="https://booksandbao.com/9-translated-dystopian-novels/">best translated dystopian novels</a>. They are the ultimate book champions of translated literature, and their choices, just like them, are simply wonderful.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2025/01/19/10-beautiful-book-blogs-to-follow/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
