<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Shop &#8211; Notebookish</title>
	<atom:link href="/shop/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 11:57:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>International Fuel Gas Code 2021</title>
		<link>/product/international-fuel-gas-code-2021/</link>
					<comments>/product/international-fuel-gas-code-2021/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 05:47:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=276</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Addresses the design and installation of fuel gas systems and gas fired appliances through prescriptive and performance requirements. Key changes...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Addresses the design and installation of fuel gas systems and gas fired appliances through prescriptive and performance requirements. Key changes in the 2021 IFGC include: The termination of concealed condensate piping requires marking to indicate if it is the primary drain or the secondary drain. Press-connect joints are acceptable for high pressure (over 5 psi) applications indoors. Commercial cooking appliances are not allowed within dwelling units.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/product/international-fuel-gas-code-2021/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>TEXTBOOK OF NEONATAL RESUSCITATION 8ED</title>
		<link>/product/textbook-of-neonatal-resuscitation-8ed/</link>
					<comments>/product/textbook-of-neonatal-resuscitation-8ed/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 05:44:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=272</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Neonatal Resuscitation Program® (NRP®) course conveys an evidence-based approach to care of the newborn at birth and facilitates effective...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Neonatal Resuscitation Program® (NRP®) course conveys an evidence-based approach to care of the newborn at birth and facilitates effective team-based care for healthcare professionals who care for newborns at the time of delivery. NRP utilizes a blended learning approach, which includes online testing and hands-on case-based simulation/debriefing that focus on critical leadership, communication, and team-work skills.​​The NRP, 8th Edition, introduces a new educational methodology to better meet the needs of health care professionals who manage the newly born baby. New in the 8th edition:Key Points at the beginning of each lesson.Quick response (QR) codes that enable the reader to view short videos about the topic on their mobile device.Lesson Review Questions grouped together at the end of each lesson.Quality Improvement Opportunities and Frequently Asked Questions in each lesson.New sections in Lesson 10 (Special Considerations) about resuscitation of the newborn with a myelomeningocele or an abdominal wall defect.Three Supplemental Lessons (Improving Resuscitation Team Performance, Resuscitation Outside the Delivery Room, and Bringing Quality Improvement to Your Resuscitation Team) that all NRP users to enhance their resuscitation knowledge and performance.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/product/textbook-of-neonatal-resuscitation-8ed/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Essentials of Strength Training and Conditioning</title>
		<link>/product/essentials-of-strength-training-and-conditioning/</link>
					<comments>/product/essentials-of-strength-training-and-conditioning/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 09:38:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=100</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Developed by the National Strength and Conditioning Association (NSCA) and now in its fourth edition, Essentials of Strength Training and Conditioning is...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Developed by the National Strength and Conditioning Association (NSCA) and now in its fourth edition, <span class="a-text-italic">Essentials of Strength Training and Conditioning</span> is the essential text for strength and conditioning professionals and students. This comprehensive resource, created by 30 expert contributors in the field, explains the key theories, concepts, and scientific principles of strength training and conditioning as well as their direct application to athletic competition and performance.</p>
<p>The scope and content of <span class="a-text-italic">Essentials of Strength Training and Conditioning, Fourth Edition With HKPropel Access,</span> have been updated to convey the knowledge, skills, and abilities required of a strength and conditioning professional and to address the latest information found on the Certified Strength and Conditioning Specialist (CSCS) exam. The evidence-based approach and unbeatable accuracy of the text make it the primary resource to rely on for CSCS exam preparation.</p>
<p>The text is organized to lead readers from theory to program design and practical strategies for administration and management of strength and conditioning facilities. The fourth edition contains the most current research and applications and several new features:</p>
<ul class="a-unordered-list a-vertical">
<li><span class="a-list-item">Online videos featuring 21 resistance training exercises demonstrate proper exercise form for classroom and practical use.</span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">Updated research&amp;;specifically in the areas of high-intensity interval training, overtraining, agility and change of direction, nutrition for health and performance, and periodization&amp;;helps readers better understand these popular trends in the industry.</span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">A new chapter with instructions and photos presents techniques for exercises using alternative modes and nontraditional implements.</span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">Ten additional tests, including those for maximum strength, power, and aerobic capacity, along with new flexibility exercises, resistance training exercises, plyometric exercises, and speed and agility drills help professionals design programs that reflect current guidelines.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>Key points, chapter objectives, and learning aids including key terms and self-study questions provide a structure to help students and professionals conceptualize the information and reinforce fundamental facts. Application sidebars provide practical application of scientific concepts that can be used by strength and conditioning specialists in real-world settings, making the information immediately relatable and usable. Online learning tools delivered through HK<span class="a-text-italic">Propel</span> provide students with 11 downloadable lab activities for practice and retention of information. Further, both students and professionals will benefit from the online videos of 21 foundational exercises that provide visual instruction and reinforce proper technique.</p>
<p><span class="a-text-italic">Essentials of Strength Training and Conditioning, Fourth Edition,</span> provides the most comprehensive information on organization and administration of facilities, testing and evaluation, exercise techniques, training adaptations, program design, and structure and function of body systems. Its scope, precision, and dependability make it the essential preparation text for the CSCS exam as well as a definitive reference for strength and conditioning professionals to consult in their everyday practice.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/product/essentials-of-strength-training-and-conditioning/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ACSM&#8217;s Guidelines for Exercise Testing and Prescription</title>
		<link>/product/acsms-guidelines-for-exercise-testing-and-prescription/</link>
					<comments>/product/acsms-guidelines-for-exercise-testing-and-prescription/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 09:34:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=97</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Lippincott® Connect Featured TitlePurchase of the new print edition of this Lippincott® Connect title includes lifetime access to the digital...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lippincott® Connect Featured TitlePurchase of the new print edition of this Lippincott® Connect title includes lifetime access to the digital version of the book, plus related materials such as videos and multiple-choice Q&amp;A and self-assessments.The flagship title from the prestigious American College of Sports Medicine, this critical handbook delivers scientifically based, evidence-informed standards to prepare you for success. Providing succinct summaries of recommended procedures for exercise testing and exercise prescription in healthy and diseased patients, this trusted manual is an essential resource for all exercise professionals, as well as other health professionals who may counsel patients on exercise including physicians, nurses, physician assistants, physical and occupational therapists, dieticians, and health care administrators. The extensively updated eleventh edition has been reorganized for greater clarity and integrates the latest Physical Activity Guidelines for Americans.UPDATED! Integrated guidelines, including the 2018 Physical Activity Guidelines for Americans, reflect the most current, clinically sound approaches to exercise testing and prescription.NEW! Chapter on conditions that affect the brain familiarizes students with specific strategies for the treatment of Parkinson’s disease, Alzheimer’s disease, autism, depression and anxiety. UPDATED! Enhanced organization helps students find information quickly and easily.    FITT (Frequency, Intensity, Time, Type) boxes make locating critical exercise prescription information quick and easy.Revised appendices integrate valuable information on ECGs, medication and emergency management where it is most relevant. A new appendix on metabolic equations is included.Additional boxes, tables, and figures highlight important concepts and approaches at a glance.  Lippincott® Connect features: Lifetime access to the digital version of the book with the ability to highlight and take notes on key passages for a more personal, efficient study experience.Carefully curated resources, such as interactive diagrams, video tutorials, organ sounds, and self-assessment, all designed to facilitate further comprehension.Lippincott® Connect also allows users to create Study Collections to further personalize the study experience. With Study Collections you can: Pool content from books across your entire library into self-created Study Collections based on discipline, procedure, organ, concept or other topics.Display related text passages, video clips and self-assessment questions from each book (if available) for efficient absorption of material.Annotate and highlight key content for easy access later.Navigate seamlessly between book chapters, sections, self-assessments, notes and highlights in a single view/page.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/product/acsms-guidelines-for-exercise-testing-and-prescription/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PRISCRIBER&#8217;S GUIDE</title>
		<link>/product/priscribers-guide/</link>
					<comments>/product/priscribers-guide/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 09:29:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=92</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Genetic counselors translate the findings of scientific investigation into meaningful accounts that enable individuals and families to make decisions about...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Genetic counselors translate the findings of scientific investigation into meaningful accounts that enable individuals and families to make decisions about their lives</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/product/priscribers-guide/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EVIDENCE BASED PRACTICE IN NURSING</title>
		<link>/product/evidence-based-practice-in-nursing/</link>
					<comments>/product/evidence-based-practice-in-nursing/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 08:38:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=83</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[For twenty years, the lessons from The Pragmatic Programmer have helped a generation of programmers examine the very essence of software development, independent of...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For <span class="a-text-bold">twenty years</span>, the lessons from <span class="a-text-bold">The Pragmatic Programmer</span> have helped a generation of programmers examine the very essence of <span class="a-text-bold">software development</span>, independent of any particular language, framework, or methodology. This classic title is regularly featured on “Top Ten” lists, and many corporations issue it to their new hires. This new <span class="a-text-bold a-text-italic">20th Anniversary Edition offers a fresh look</span> at the modern development landscape, cutting through the “business as usual” and tired advice from the net to help guide you through the next twenty years and beyond. Featuring new tips, new topics, and revisions throughout, you don’t want to miss this one. Published by <span class="a-text-italic">Addison Wesley by special arrangement with the Pragmatic Bookshelf.</span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/product/evidence-based-practice-in-nursing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>WRITING YOUR JOURNAL ARTICLE</title>
		<link>/product/writing-your-journal-article/</link>
					<comments>/product/writing-your-journal-article/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 08:29:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=79</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[&#8220;Wow. No one ever told me this!&#8221; Wendy Laura Belcher has heard this countless times throughout her years of teaching...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Wow. No one ever told me this!&#8221; Wendy Laura Belcher has heard this countless times throughout her years of teaching and advising academics on how to write journal articles. Scholars know they must publish, but few have been told how to do so. So Belcher made it her mission to demystify the writing process. The result was Writing Your Journal Article in Twelve Weeks, which takes this overwhelming task and breaks it into small, manageable steps. For the past decade, this guide has been the go-to source for those creating articles for peer-reviewed journals. It has enabled thousands to overcome their anxieties and produce the publications that are essential to succeeding in their fields. With this new edition, Belcher expands her advice to reach beginning scholars in even more disciplines. She builds on feedback from professors and graduate students who have successfully used the workbook to complete their articles. A new chapter addresses scholars who are writing from scratch. This edition also includes more targeted exercises and checklists, as well as the latest research on productivity and scholarly writing. Writing Your Journal Article in Twelve Weeks is the only reference to combine expert guidance with a step-by-step workbook. Each week, readers learn a feature of strong articles and work on revising theirs accordingly. Every day is mapped out, taking the guesswork and worry out of writing. There are tasks, templates, and reminders. At the end of twelve weeks, graduate students, recent PhDs, postdoctoral fellows, adjunct instructors, junior faculty, and international faculty will feel confident they know that the rules of academic publishing and have the tools they need to succeed.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/product/writing-your-journal-article/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DSM-5 PAPERBACK</title>
		<link>/product/dsm-5-paperback/</link>
					<comments>/product/dsm-5-paperback/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 08:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=74</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[DIAGNOSTIC AND STATISTICAL MANUAL OF MENTAL DISORDERS TEXT REVISION DSM 5 TR 5ED (PB 2022)]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DIAGNOSTIC AND STATISTICAL MANUAL OF MENTAL DISORDERS TEXT REVISION DSM 5 TR 5ED (PB 2022)</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/product/dsm-5-paperback/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
